Sergey Lubimov

Software Engineer

Belarus https://www.linkedin.com/in/sergey-lubimov/

SUMMARY

Over 10 years relevant experience in web development with more than 15 years in IT (started as System Administrator).

SKILLS

Node.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, AWS Express, Fastify, Nest.js, Moleculer, OpenAPI/Swagger Jest, Mocha, Chai, Sinon, Supertest React, Redux, HTML, CSS, JSX MySQL, PostgreSQL, DynamoDB, MongoDB, TypeORM, Sequelize, Prisma Docker, Webpack, Vite

LANGUAGES

English B2 Intermediate \cdot Russian Native \cdot Belorussian Native

EXPERIENCE

Software Development Engineer
EPAM Systems · Full-time · Jan 2022 - Present

Software Engineer
BisonSoft · Full-time · Feb 2020 - Oct 2021

Web development & System Administration
Belita-Vitex-Mogilev, LCC · Full-time · Apr 2015 - Nov 2019

PROJECTS

Grabli - Automation tool to grab CVs from Linkedin to corporate HR CRM.
STACK: NodeJS, MongoDB, Mangoose, Moleculer, Chrome Extension, Vue
JAN 2023 - JUL 2023

Joe and the Juice - App to order food worldwide with loyalty system. STACK: NodeJS, MongoDB, Sequelize, ReactNative, Jest NOV 2022 - JAN 2023 https://www.joejuice.com/app

Bayer Loem - Loyalty program of Bayer Corp. for Ukrainian farmers Period: JAN 2022 - NOV 2022

STACK: AWS, SAM, NodeJS, SQL, PostgreSQL

EDUCATION

Belarusian State Economic University, Minsk, Belarus - 1992 - 1997 Post-graduate education 1997 - 2000 Specialization: Economic Cybernetic